<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

    <string id="st_ammo-6.8x43_fmj">
        <text>6.8x43 FMJ</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo-6.8x43_fmj_descr">
        <text>The 6.8 Remington Special Purpose round is a rifle round that was developed by Remington Arms in collaboration with members of the U.S. Army to possibly replace the 5.56 NATO round. It is midway between the 5.56x45mm NATO and 7.62x51mm NATO in diameter and muzzle energy, slightly more powerful than the 7.62x39 round.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_ammo-6.8x43_sst">
        <text>6.8x43 SST</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo-6.8x43_sst_descr">
        <text>Short for "Super Shock Tip" the SST round is designed to deliver tremendous shock on impact while expanding quickly and reliably.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_ammo-6.8x43_ap">
        <text>6.8x43 AP</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo-6.8x43_ap_descr">
        <text>6.8x43 armor piercing round designed for optimal body armor penetration.</text>
    </string>


    <string id="st_sil_68">
        <text>6.8 Suppressor</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_sil_68_descr">
        <text>Suppressor for 6.8x43 assault rifles</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hk416d">
		<text>HK416D</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hk416d_descr">
		<text>The HK416 is a rifle designed and manufactured by Heckler &amp; Koch to improve the M4. It is available as a complete firearm, or as an upper receiver that fits on any AR-15 type lower receiver. The US Army's Delta Force collaborated with the German arms makers to develop the new rifle. Testing the H&amp;K 416 in 2004 revealed that the piston operating system significantly reduces malfunctions while increasing the life of parts. The project was originally called the H&amp;K M4, but was changed in response to a trademark infringement suit filed by Colt Defence. Currently, it is only available to government and military organisations, hence why this assault rifle is usually carried by Mercenaries.\n
		While looking exactly like the HK416, this HK416D model is chambered for 6.8 SPC, and only fabricated by H&K under private contract; you can only guess how this gun came into the Zone.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6.8 Suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_lr680">
        <text>LR-680</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_lr680_descr">
        <text>A variant of the 5.56x45mm LR-300 assault rifle chambered for the larger 6.8mm SPC round. Due to its larger round, its fire rate is noticeably lower compared to the standard LR-300, but features a higher damage output.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6.8 Suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m4bm">
        <text>Bushmaster M4</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_m4bm_descr">
        <text>The Bushmaster M4 is a copy of the popular M4 carbine manufactured by Bushmaster Firearms International, modeled on the AR-15 platform and chambered in 6.8 SPC.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6.8 Suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m4_brec7">
        <text>Barrett REC7</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_m4_brec7_descr">
        <text>Based on the M16 rifle, this weapon fires the more powerful 6.8x43 SPC round and fires in semi-automatic and full automatic firemodes, boosting higher firepower then its 5.56x45mm variant but higher recoil due to its larger round.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6.8 Suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher (after modification)
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_m249_nimble">
        <text>M68</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_m249_nimble_descr">
        <text>The M68 is a customized M249 machine gun rechambered in 6.8 SPC.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6.8 Suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_ar15_68">
        <text>AR-15 - 6.8x43</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ar15_68_descr">
        <text>The AR-15 is a 5.56x45 semi-automatic version of the M4 assault rifle marketed to civilians. Can mount a suppressor and optics, but not a grenade launcher.\n
		This particular version is chambered in 6.8 SPC, increasing its hitting power in exchange of range.
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 6.8 Suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes</text>
    </string>

<!-- BaS -->
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru55668">
		<text>Ruger SR-556/6.8 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru55668_descr">
		<text>Several of these rifles entered the Zone through scientists. According to legend, Professor Sakharov received 6 small containers with these guns from foreign sponsors, but 5 of them were lost during transportation. Ruger SR-556 is an American self-loading carbine manufactured by the arms company Sturm, Ruger & Company, Inc. became the first Ruger of the AR-10 family. Ruger SR-762 chambered for .308. Belongs to a few samples of AR-15 rifles using the removal of powder gases. Production ceased in January 2016 after the introduction of the Keymod Lightweight option.\n
		This SR-556/6.8 version was a later variant chambered in 6.8.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Universal mount by NcStar with Trijicon RMR red dot sight installed on it. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:  All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: 6.8 suppressor</text>
	</string>


<!-- Mags -->
	<string id="st_mag_68_default">
		<text>Standard 6.8 SPC magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_68_default_descr">
		<text>28-round magazine used by 6.8 SPC rifles during their infancy. Very similar to the standard 30 round AR-15/M16 magazines in 5.56x45, it is relatively cheap and light.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_68_heavy">
		<text>Heavy 6.8 SPC magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_68_heavy_descr">
		<text>30-round magazine compatible with 6.8 SPC rifles. Heavier than the more common magazine model, due to the need for more space to fit the magic 30 number.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_68_fast">
		<text>Fast-loading 6.8 SPC magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_68_fast_descr">
		<text>30-round magazine compatible with 6.8 SPC rifles. Designed with less steel than the standard magazine, and more thought on facilitating the quick loading of rounds.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_68_short">
		<text>Short 6.8 SPC magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_68_short_descr">
		<text>25-round magazine compatible with 6.8 SPC rifles. It provides a relatively decent load capability in a small size. It's also quick to load.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_68_extended">
		<text>Extended 6.8 SPC magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_68_extended_descr">
		<text>Extended 40-round polymer magazine compatible with 6.8 SPC rifles. Bigger and heavier than other extended mags, but not so much to matter a lot.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_68_casket">
		<text>60-round 6.8 SPC magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_68_casket_descr">
		<text>60-round quad-stack magazine compatible with 6.8 SPC rifles. Offers a lot of firepower, but is extremely heavy and the quad-stack nature makes it difficult to load in rounds quickly.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_68_cmag">
		<text>100-round 6.8 SPC Beta C-Mag</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_68_cmag_descr">
		<text>100-round dual drum magazine compatible with 6.8 SPC rifles. Offers a lot of firepower, but is extremely heavy and time consuming to load.\n
		Strangely, you can't see the sign of any manufacturer, but the production seems well made.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_m249_68">
		<text>6.8 SPC M249 Box</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_m249_68_descr">
		<text>A standard 5.56x45 M249 Box converted for 100 6.8 SPC rounds. Not much of a reason to do this, unless you are somehow aware of a M249 variant chambered for 6.8.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>