<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
<!-- 
    <string id="ammo-10x22_fmj">
        <text>.40 S&amp;W FMJ</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ammo-10x22_fmj_descr">
        <text>Full metal jacket .40 S&amp;W (10x22mm) rounds. The .40 S&amp;W round has been popular with law enforcement agencies in the United States, Canada, and Australia. While possessing nearly identical accuracy, drift and drop it is much more powerful than the 9x19 round and with more manageable recoil than the 10mm Auto.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ammo-10x22_hp">
        <text>.40 S&amp;W JHP</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ammo-10x22_hp_descr">
        <text>Jacketed Hollow point .40 S&amp;W (10x22mm) rounds. The bullet fragments on impact with soft tissue maximizing tissue damage, blood loss and shock. The .40 S&amp;W round has been popular with law enforcement agencies in the United States, Canada, and Australia. While possessing nearly identical accuracy, drift and drop it is much more powerful than the 9x19 round and with more manageable recoil than the 10mm Auto.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ammo-10x22_ap">
        <text>.40 S&amp;W AP</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ammo-10x22_ap_descr">
        <text>Armor piercing .40 S&amp;W rounds.</text>
    </string>
 -->
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_40">
        <text>CZ 75 .40 S&amp;W</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_cz75_40_descr">
        <text>The CZ-75 was developed in the Czech Republic by the Koucky brothers. This semi-automatic pistol first appeared in 1975, entered production in 1976 and was intended for the export market. The CZ-75 accumulated the best features from many preceding designs and the resulting pistol was aesthetically attractive, comfortable to handle, shoot, accurate and reliable in operation. Made by CZ arms in various versions and modifications, the CZ-75 was also widely copied and cloned.\n
		This variant of the CZ 75 is chambered in .40S&amp;W, and features an increased in stopping power and lighter weight, but its main drawbacks are an increase in recoil, and lower magazine capacity.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 10mm suppressor -->
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech suppressor
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_glock35">
        <text>Glock 35</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_glock35_descr">
        <text>The Glock 35 is the .40 S&amp;W model of the Glock pistol series first introduced in 1990, beginning with the Glock 22. It features a slighty lower capacity compared to the Glock 19, but improves upon the accuracy and fire rate.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DeltaPoint Sight \n -->
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 10mm suppressor \n -->
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech suppressor
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_fnp40">
        <text>FNP-40</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fnp40_descr">
        <text>The FN FNP pistol is a series of semi-automatic, polymer framed pistols manufactured in Columbia, South Carolina by FNH USA, a division of Fabrique Nationale de Herstal. Debuted in early 2006, the FNP series weapons are hammer fired weapons utilizing a Browning cam system with an external extractor. The trigger module is housed inside the polymer frame as an individual unit connected to the hammer. The magazine release button is held in place by a retention pin which can be removed to allow the button to be reversed.\n 
		The FN FNP-40 pistol is a variant of the FNP-45 chambered in .40 S&amp;W. It is notablly more accurate but features a lower damage output compared to its .45 variant.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DeltaPoint Sight \n -->
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 10mm suppressor \n -->
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech suppressor
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_usp40">
        <text>USP-40</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp40_descr">
        <text>Originally designed for the American market, the USP, Universal Self loading Pistol, is known as an accurate and reliable handgun. U.S. law enforcement and military provided much of the design criteria for the USP. The controls are uniquely American, influenced by famous designs like the Government Model 1911 pistol. All USPs use a fibre-reinforced polymer frame stiffened by stainless steel inserts at areas subject to stress and friction. Incorporating several successful handgun design elements, the USP Compact .45 is a part of the USP family of handguns designed by H&amp;K. Able to withstand extreme punishment and adverse conditions, it is used by several countries' police and special forces units.\n
		Developed around the same time as its .45 variant, the USP-40 is chambered .40 S&amp;W rounds. Compared to its .45 ACP and 10mm Auto cousins, it features considerably lower recoil and lighter weight. Its drawbacks include its still considerable size, and lower damage output.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DeltaPoint Sight \n -->
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 10mm suppressor -->
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech suppressor
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_walther40">
        <text>Walther P99 .40 S&amp;W</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_walther40_descr">
        <text>Ergonomics being a key focus in its design, the Walther P99 is a recoil-operated pistol with a fibreglass polymer frame. Developed for law enforcement and the civilian shooting market, it's employed by police units in a number of countries.\n 
		This is a variant chambered for the .40S&amp;W round, featuring lower recoil and slighty lower weight.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] DeltaPoint Sight \n -->
		<!-- %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 10mm suppressor -->
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Gemtech suppressor
		</text>
    </string>

</string_table>